《Show Yourself》
Every inch of me is trembling
我身体的每一寸都在打颤
But not from the cold
但并不是因为严寒
Something is familiar
有一种熟悉的感觉
Like a dream I can reach but not quite hold
如梦一般，可望而不可及
I can sense you there
我能感觉到你在那里
Like a friend I've always known
像我相识多年的故友
I'm arriving
我来了
And it feels like I am home
好像回到了家中
I have always been a fortress
过去我如同一座堡垒
Cold secrets deep inside
冰冷的秘密往深处藏
You have secrets too
你也有你的秘密
But you don't have to hide
但你没必要隐瞒
Show yourself
现身吧
I'm dying to meet you
我渴望遇见你
Show yourself
现身吧
It's your turn
轮到你了
Are you the one I've been looking for
你是不是我穷尽毕生
All of my life
都在寻找的答案
Show yourself
现身吧
I'm ready to learn
我已准备好去知晓
Ah ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah ah
I've never felt so certain
我从未感到如此确信
All my life I've been torn
在我这破碎的一生里
But I'm here for a reason
但冥冥之中指引我到这里
Could it be the reason I was born
是否在我出生起便已注定
I have always been so different
我天生就与众不同
Normal rules did not apply
打破偏见超越传统
Is this the day
是不是今天
Are you the way
是不是你
I finally find out why
能助我揭晓一切的真相
Show yourself
现身吧
I'm no longer trembling
我已经不再惧怕
Here I am
就现在
I've come so far
我千里迢迢而来
You are the answer I've waited for
你是我耗尽毕生时间
All of my life
等待的答案
Oh show yourself
现身吧
Let me see who you are
让我看看你是谁
Come to me now
向我走来
Open your door
打开大门
Don't make me wait
别让我再有
One moment more
哪怕半刻等待
Oh come to me now
向我走来
Open your door
打开大门
Don't make me wait
别让我再有
One moment more
哪怕半刻等待
Where the north wind meets the sea
北风吹过，海浪起
There's a river
有一条河流
Full of memory
充满回忆
Come my darling homeward bound
来吧宝贝，快回到家里
I am found
发现我自己
Show yourself
现身吧
Step into your power
踏入你的魔力里
Grow yourself
成长吧
Into something new
发现崭新的自己
You are the one you've been waiting for
你是你穷尽毕生的时间
All of my life
等待的答案
Oh show yourself
现身吧
Ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah
我拿两个6寸水果味的匹萨
换你一个人11寸的披萨  换吗？
我一个半小时没有把自己介绍完
布丁奶茶店：Could u sing「愛してるばんざーい!」?
加班
写不完自我介绍
8-18
这个...这个可以洗吗？
这个也可以洗吗？
可以洗吧
可以洗
都可以洗  洗她的衣服
373...单推人...吾哲...16
"初见，suki，单推，结婚否？"
我...我...我不是很懂你
能不能结婚
我要...我要跟美少女结婚
"老板断气"
我的...胖次是什么颜色的
啊...
啊...啊...
啊...啊...啊...
我...我告诉你
我告诉你别人的胖次是什么颜色的
可以吗？
"Can you marry me?"
你要...你要知道谁的？
我...
我刚...
我是蒙面大盗
"内衣大盗，偷了姐姐们的衣服回家悄悄洗了！"